http://www.statetheatrenj.org/privacy-policy

×'TIS THE SEASON OF GIVING!
Give a tax-deductible gift by Dec. 31st and help State Theatre continue to provide inspiration and entertainment through the power of the performing arts! DONATE NOW >
Events & ProgramsUpcoming EventsFlex TicketsGift CertificatesOnline Culture FixOnline Trivia NightsPlay at HomeEducation & Community EngagementEnhance Your ExperienceSpecial EventsSensory-Friendly PerformancesGroupsThirty30 ClubCOVID ResponseCOVID ResponseLetter from the President & CEOSupport UsDonate NowJoin UsNext Stage CampaignSpecial EventsCorporate PartnershipCurrent PartnersCurrent SupportersMatching GIftsDonor-Advised FundsLeave a LegacyShopNext Stage CampaignThe CampaignA Letter from the President & CEOThe DetailsCampaign LeadershipNaming OpportunitiesDonor ListingIn The NewsSupport Us NowExploreShare Your StoryMagazineSTNJ PodcastsAboutHistoryInformation & PoliciesOfficial Ticket SourcesAnnual ReportBoard of TrusteesBecome a VolunteerYour VisitSite SearchE-News SignupLoginSign Up
Privacy Policy
State Theatre New Jersey is committed to respecting the privacy of its customers and all visitors of the State Theatre website. The following document details the policies that State Theatre New Jersey has in place to safeguard your privacy. By using our website and creating an account, you are agreeing to the policies below.
Collection of Information
State Theatre New Jersey uses the personal information it collects to process your orders, to notify you of event changes and updates, and to personalize your website experience, offering you unique ticket offers or event invitations based on your interests.
When you create an account on www.STNJ.org you share your first name, last name, and email address with us. Your mailing address is required to purchase tickets, enter a contest, or make a contribution. When transacting a sale, we will also require your credit card number. In certain jurisdictions, such as the European Union, you may have specific rights to access, change, transfer or request removal of personal information about you. If you have requests or questions concerning use of your personal information please email info@stnj.org.
State Theatre New Jersey may share information with various entities such as third party renters as part of fulfillment of VIP or other programs presented by these entities. When you make a purchase in connection with a performance presented or produced by a third party organization, State Theatre will provide said third party with the information regarding your purchase. This information may include, but shall not be limited to, your name, address, telephone number and email address, as well as details of your purchase, which may include, but shall not be limited to, the date you purchased your tickets, any offer you responded to, the locations of your seats, and the dollar amount of your transaction.
Mailing address information is never sold, rented or freely given to any outside entity. Mailing address information may be traded with other nonprofit arts companies for a one-time usage through a third-party mail house or service. This is common industry practice.
Email Addresses
Email addresses are never sold or rented. If you don’t want to receive periodic email notices from State Theatre New Jersey, or would like to make changes to the types of emails your receive, visit the “My Account” section of STNJ.org which is visible in the upper right hand corner of this page when you are signed into your account. You may also email info@stnj.org to unsubscribe. Please note, we may still email you with important information (show cancellations, changes, etc.)  about events you have tickets to even if you have unsubscribed from marketing and fundraising emails.
Links
State Theatre New Jersey's website may include links to other websites. We do not control the privacy policies of the destination sites. Once you leave our servers (you can check where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site that you are visiting. That policy may differ from State Theatre New Jersey's policies. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from such a site's homepage, you should contact the manager of that site for more information. State Theatre is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites other than the its own website.
Financial Information
State Theatre New Jersey will protect any financial information you provide to us. If you purchase merchandise online, your credit card is encrypted using current secure communication technologies. Your credit card number will only be used for processing orders. For reasons of security, credit card information is not stored on our Web Servers. We restrict access to customer financial information for use by authorized State Theatre New Jersey authorized personnel only.
Cookies
Cookies are small bits of data transferred to your computer by a website to facilitate your online experience. Cookies are only used to assist in customer log-in functions, track the progress of e-commerce transactions, and to record session information in order to analyze website effectiveness. We do not share information obtained by cookies with other organizations on an individual basis. This information may be shared with other organizations in a summary format.
Passwords
When you create an account online, you will be asked to select a password, in order to protect your account. Passwords are kept confidential and do not allow access to payment information such as credit card numbers, etc. If you have trouble signing into your account, please email info@stnj.org.
Comments on Social Media Platforms
We are pleased to offer our community an opportunity to share diverse opinions and varied points of view on our social media pages—in fact, we encourage it! Our goal is to build community through the arts and, as such, we do require that all comments follow a few basic standards. Comments that are threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or racist will be removed. We require that all comments are free from profanity and hate speech. All comments should be relevant to the post and remain respectful of other commenters.
Security and Disclaimer
Although we use security that we believe to be appropriate to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee that our security precautions will protect against, and we expressly disclaim any liability for, any loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
State Theatre New Jersey, from time to time, may update this policy without prior notice. Changes to this policy will be reflected on the theater's website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please email us at info@stnj.org.
X
Events forAllAugust 2021September 2021October 2021November 2021March 2022X9 Shows FoundABBA The Concert8/8The Righteous Brothers8/12Straight No Chaser9/19Golden Oldies Spectacular9/25Complexions Contemporary Ballet10/19Million Dollar Quartet11/2The Temptations & The Four Tops11/7British Invasion/Doo Wop Spectacular11/13Diavolo3/25Choose Seats X  Make aDonationBuy TicketsChoose A Show...
X
Choose Seats...0 ItemsExpires in
The State Theatre does NOT have an elevator. If you need downstairs accessible...
An Evening with Sarod MaestroAt State Theatre New Jersey12/15/2105 7:00pm
Choose a Section
Choose seat widget here
Switch to Best Available SeatingApply$0.00 for 0 itemsAdd to Cart
